Surprise!
A Prime Minister's panel
convened.
Olmert declared, "I did
not ask for this!
" It
felt like a sudden, venomous
spider bite.
The Lebanon War
spawned two investigative panels;
an
immediate attack.
Everything crumbled spectacularly.
The Winograd investigation resembled a
relentless SHIELD interrogation.
Secret negotiations
offered Jerusalem.
They even suggested,
"Take the Infinity Gauntlet!
" Imagine
wielding that immense power.
Corruption
panels revealed a Hydra-like proliferation
of wrongdoing.
Cash envelopes rained
down, a torrential storm of
illicit funds.
Then came the
prison sentence.
The removal of
his power, like stripping Iron
Man of his armor, began
with a clang.
Prison stripes.
The first Prime Minister imprisoned.
A hollow cell echo resonated.
He reflected, "I almost achieved peace.
" A memoir's poignant thought bubble:
"If only they knew...
"