Behold, a baby dragon perched atop an
endless
staircase!
Monotonic means always ascending or always
descending.
This dragon is never falling.
Bounded and monotonic
implies convergence.
The dragon is trapped, caught in
a time loop!
Each step in this recursive
sequence depends on the previous one.
We can
determine the limits of these sequences.
It mirrors
the dragon's journey.
The number *e* symbol of
natural dragon growth, a key mathematical
constant.
Observe
Cantor's dragon boxes, each smaller than
the last.
Subsequences are like the dragon's kin,
related yet
distinct.
The Bolzano-Weierstrass theorem assures
bounded sequence possesses
a convergent subsequence.
The dragon always finds its way