Distinguished faculty, esteemed guests,
fellow
graduates.
Today marks a momentous
occasion.
My name is Bibi
Netanyahu;
I am from Israel.
I am ready to lead.
A narrow victory, just one
percent separated me from my
opponent.
The people have spoken.
The Western Wall tunnel opening
unleashed chaos.
Spirits escaped, dissolving
peace.
Cigars and champagne flowed;
a celebratory atmosphere filled the
air.
Sara, however, entered a
furious rage.
She unleashed her
anger upon my political foes.
The coalition unexpectedly collapsed.
My
heroic allies scattered.
I disbanded
the ranks.
I will return,
stronger and more determined.
I
will practice in mirrors, honing
my image.
One day, I
will be the longest-serving leader.
My vision for Israel is clear, unwavering,
and powerful.
I will not be deterred.
I will prevail.