Behold Ehud Barak, Israel's most decorated
soldier.
His medals shone, a dazzling display.
They
called him Israel's most brilliant Prime
Minister.
His intellect was renowned.
At Camp David,
he proposed a peace deal, a bold
initiative.
Yet, Yasser Arafat rejected his every
proposal.
The Second Intifada erupted, a devastating
conflict.
Barak, a man of many facets,
once undertook a clandestine operation in
disguise.
He demonstrated a remarkable understanding
of gender
fluidity.
His coalition government fractured, a
swift
and tragic collapse.
Victory eluded him;
he
suffered a crushing defeat to Ariel
Sharon.
It was a historic loss.
Later, on
Epstein's island, he famously quipped, "I
kept my underwear on!
" Now, he reflects on his legacy.