The Rial's value has plummeted.
Mathematicians created new numbers to
describe it.
Peter Griffin, our impromptu economist,
comments, "The economy is like my diet -
" A Quagmire-esque trader shouts,
"Giggity!
My house for that sandwich!
" This economic chaos continues, impacting
markets globally.
The situation is dire, affecting everyday
people.
Experts predict further instability.
Citizens are worried about their savings.
The government is scrambling for
solutions.
A sense of uncertainty hangs heavy in the
air.
International markets react with
volatility.
The future remains uncertain.
This unprecedented crisis demands
immediate action.
We will continue to provide updates as the
situation unfolds