Shamir, ant-sized, declared, 'Size
matters not!
' Flashback:
Underground
fighting memories, brutal and
swift, like the Winter
Soldier.
A musical chairs
sequence showed the Prime
Minister's throne switching with
Peres's;
a dramatic swap!
Intifada panels flashed:
stones
against tanks, David versus
Goliath;
a clang of
desperate conflict.
He was
dragged to the Madrid
Conference, a desperate plea
escaping him, 'No!
' Bush
Senior loomed, a mega-threat.
'Your loans...
gone!
' An
immovable object panel declared,
'Not one inch!
' It
met an unstoppable force;
a catastrophic crash.
Defeat:
votes scattered like dust.
He declared, his voice booming, 'Terror?
I invented it!
' A mic drop.
BOOM!