Welcome back to Iran International News.
I
am your anchor, Maryam.
We have breaking
news:
Scientists confirm water has vanished from
Iran.
It is a complete disappearance.
We
now go to a government official for
comment.
Sir, what is your response to
this water crisis?
Water?
I have not
heard of her.
Is she single?
Meanwhile,
desperate citizens are seen collecting
morning dew
from car surfaces.
A truly resourceful, yet
heartbreaking, situation unfolds as this
unexpected crisis
deepens.
The lack of water impacts agriculture,
daily life, and threatens public health.
Experts
warn of a severe humanitarian crisis
unless
immediate action is taken.
International aid organizations
are preparing emergency relief packages.
The government
is under immense pressure to provide
solutions.
Citizens are organizing protests,
demanding answers and
action.
The situation is dire, and the
future remains uncertain.
The government's nonchalant response
is adding to public outrage.
We will continue to provide updates as
this critical situation evolves.
Please stay tuned for further
developments.