All aboard the Sequence Express!
Each
car represents a , a₂, a₃…
CHOO CHOO!
We are headed to
the limit.
This train journey approaches
station L.
Convergence means approaching closer
and closer.
The Epsilon tunnel brings
us within epsilon of L.
What
a feat!
The unique limit theorem
guarantees only one destination.
No detours
are permitted.
Bounded sequences remain on
track, never straying too far.
They
are dependable travelers.
The arithmetic of
limits functions , multiplication, all
work
perfectly.
It is mathematical magic!
The
Sandwich theorem is a delightful delicious
sequence sandwich!
Even epsilon chicks converge beautifully