Welcome to RETURN PANEL, the
Marvel Comics mega-episode!
Netanyahu proclaims,
"I am INEVITABLE!
" A snap,
and a twelve-year election montage
unfolds, a dizzying Strange-style time
loop.
Cartoon bomb panels depict
Kindergarten Thanos drawing, "THIS IS
IRAN!
" Trump bromance panels feature
floating hearts;
"Love you 3000!
"
he proclaims.
The corruption trial
begins:
collecting scandal stones.
Cigars,
champagne, and media frenzy surround
the proceedings.
COVID panels showcase
his claim, "I SAVED Israel!
"
Protests rage outside.
The Abraham
Accords arrive – a plot
twist!
Unexpected peace signatures are
made.
Coalition juggling ensues;
balls
drop.
CRASH!
He winks, "Back
in 2022!
" The 'King Bibi'
crown crumbles to ash.
Post-credit scene:
plotting in shadows...