Welcome to the Dragon Calculus Olympics
Dragons compete in thrilling calculus
challenges
They master the chain rule in a blazing
relay race
Inverse function derivatives are judged in
gravity-defying gymnastics
Higher derivatives and critical points are
conquered in a mountain marathon
Fermat's, Rolle's, Lagrange, and Cauchy
theorems are found in epic treasure hunts
Witness breathtaking aerial maneuvers and
intense competition
Feel the thrill of victory and the agony
of defeat
Cheering crowds roar their approval
The suspense is palpable
This is the ultimate test of mathematical
prowess and athleticism
Dragons push their limits, soaring to new
heights
The champions will be crowned