Marvel Comics finale:
Ultimate
Return!
Netanyahu returned.
Electrifying
lightning crackled.
Extremist stones
glowed, assembled on the
most right-wing panel.
A
snap attempt at judicial
reform targeted the Supreme
Court.
Resistance erupted in
furious protests.
Half of
Israel dissolved in dust,
a shocking sight.
October
7th:
the darkest day.
The security shield shattered;
Vibranium cracked.
Gaza war
panels declared total victory,
empty speech bubbles for
the hostages.
An ICC
warrant declared international villain
status.
Wanted posters plastered
the desolate land.
Polls
plummeted;
the coalition clung
precariously, held together by
Scotch tape.
'After me,
the flood!
' echoed, a Noah-like vibe.
The universe-ending panel showed him still
in power.
Post-credit:
'Democracy will return...?
' The end...
or is it?