Alright, Stewie, buckle up.
We are learning about
limits, dragon-style.
Limits are like a smooth flight,
not that teleporting nonsense.
We approach our destination
smoothly.
A perfect landing is continuity;
from any
direction, we arrive smoothly.
Epsilon-delta means getting our
flight path very close to the target
altitude.
One-sided limits are like approaching a
landing strip
from the left or the right.
A sudden
jump indicates a discontinuity.
No teleporting is allowed
mid-flight.
Continuity means our flight is a single,
unbroken path.
The Intermediate Value Theorem guarantees
we
can fly to any altitude between two points