BOOM!
The desert sand explodes as David
Ben-Gurion emerges, a figure of unwavering
resolve.
"I am inevitable!
" he proclaims, his voice
ringing with conviction.
The British Mandate dissolves
into a puff of comic smoke.
KA-POW!
Independence is declared, sweat beading on
his
brow as a new nation is born.
WHOOSH!
Even amidst the intense pressure of
cabinet meetings, Ben-Gurion maintains his
serene yoga
posture, a picture of calm amidst the
storm.
Kirby Dots energy powers the rapid
construction of kibbutzim across the newly
formed
land.
He retires to a tranquil desert
cabin, a single thought bubble above his
head:
"Finally, peace.
" But the legend is
not yet complete.
"Ben-Gurion will return...
in
1955!
" True Believer Achievement:
Created an Entire
Country.
The nation he built stands as a testament
to his vision and unwavering