Hey kids, I am Epsilon the Dragon!
Let us explore number sets.
POOF!
Natural
numbers, one, two, three, appear as
counting
cookies for my dragon treats!
But wait,
zero appears - I am special!
Negative
numbers arrive as ice one, minus two,
minus three.
Together, we are integers!
WHOOSH!
Fractions fly in as pizza ,
three-quarters.
We are rational numbers - any fraction!
The square root of two appears as
an infinite spiral dragon.
I am irrational
- my decimal never repeats!
Pi flies
by, leaving an infinite trail.
They form
the real number line.
Absolute value measures
distance from zero, like dragon hugs,
always
positive!
Intervals are dragon territories - some
include endpoints, others do not.
Bounded sets
have limits, like a dragon playpen.
For any epsilon greater than zero, we can
get closer than epsilon