Alright, Stewie, we are finding treasure
on this map section!
The Extreme Value Theorem indicates the
best and worst loot
is at the edges or peaks.
This dragon's velocity is
uniformly continuous;
it will not teleport.
Derivatives represent dragon velocity;
they show our speed at any point.
If a function
is differentiable, it is continuous,
unlike this bumpy dragon ride.
We must use this to our advantage during
this treasure
hunt.
The map shows a clear path, let us
follow
it carefully.
Remember, Stewie, patience is key to
success.
We
do not want to anger the dragon.
This treasure is
worth the effort.
Our success depends on precision and
timing.
Are you ready, Stewie?
Let us proceed with caution