Hey kids, I am Epsilon the
Dragon!
POOF!
Natural numbers magically appear
as delicious counting cookies.
But wait!
Integers arrive with a shiver,
representing
negative temperatures.
WHOOSH!
Rational numbers flutter
down as perfectly sized pizza slices.
Mind blown!
Irrational numbers are like
infinite, shimmering dragons, stretching
endlessly.
Real
numbers create a beautiful, complete
number
line.
Absolute value is a warm
dragon hug, always positive.
Intervals are
cozy nap zones on the number
line.
Bounded sets are snug, secure
cages.
Supremum is the tallest dragon
in the land!
Completeness ensures there
are no gaps on our number
line.
My little Epsilon chicks chirp, "Epsilon
is greater than zero!
"